(Raj:)He just went colon, capital O.
(Sheldon:)-You tampered with my experiment?
-We had to.
(Raj:)It was the only way to keep you
from being such a huge Dickensian.
You see that? I added the "ensian."
(Sheldon:)Did Leonard know about this?
(Sheldon:)Leonard's my best friend.
Surely Leonard didn't know.
(Howard:)-It was his idea.
-Of course it was.
(Sheldon:)The whole plan reeks of Leonard.
(Penny:)-I missed you so much.
-I missed you too.
-I couldn't think of anyone else.
-Me neither.
(Leonard:)Except for one night
when the heat went out.
Long story. It's-- Don't ask.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Leonard. Leonard. Leonard.
[WHISPERS]
Do not make a sound.
SHELDON:
Whispering, "Do not make a sound"...
(Sheldon:)...is a sound.